A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS), Community and Resource Development, Acting Director, Office Files of Carl Anthony FA507
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Trips, Conferences and Meetings, 2001-2005; IV
  - Ford Foundation RED Staff Retreat -- Community and Resource Development Unit -- Notes, Handouts, 2004 September 29-30 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation and UC Santa Cruz Center for Justice, Tolerance and Community (CJTC) Meeting Re: Camden RED Learning Agenda and Applicability to New Orleans after Hurricane Katrina, 2005 August 11-September 20 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Funders Briefing on Regional Organizing, Dearborn, MI -- Agenda, Background, 2001 December 6-7 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Funders' Network 2002 National Conference, New Orleans, LA -- Program, Background, 2002 March 4-7 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Funders' Network Regional and Neighborhood Equity Gathering, Minneapolis, MN -- Agenda, Background, 2003 April 7-11 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Funders' Network Regional and Neighborhood Equity Project Business Meeting and Equitable Development Tour, Detroit, MI -- Agenda, Background, 2004 July 22-23 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Gamaliel Foundation National Leadership Assembly, Chicago, IL -- Agenda, Background, 2002 December 5-6 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Symposium on Smart Growth, Seaside, Fl (organized by Maryland Governor's Office) -- Conference Book with Agenda, Background, 2001 November 29-December 2 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Land Bank Authority Forum (on land use and vacant property problem), Flint, MI -- Agenda, 2005 April 6-8 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Living Cities Annual Meeting, Washington, DC -- Schedule, Agenda, Background, 2005 May 10-11 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Living Cities Semi-Annual Meeting, Nov 29-30, 2005, Detroit, MI -- Correspondence, Background, Agenda, 2005 July-November (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Natural Assets in Native America -- Meeting of Practitioners of Community-Based Natural Resource Management from Native America -- Agenda, Background, 2002 March 13-15 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ohio Vacant Properties Forum, Columbus, OH -- Correspondence, Agenda, Background, 2004 October 24-25 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Urbanization, Environment and Development Seminar, Cape Town, South Africa -- Draft Program, Notes, 2005 February 25-27 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Writings, 2006; V
  This series contains a book chapter titled "Race, Poverty and the Humane Metropolis: Revisiting William H. Whyte" that Mr. Anthony wrote for The Human Metropolis: People and Nature in the Twenty-First Century City edited by Rutherford H. Platt (Amherst: University of Massachusetts Press and Lincoln Institute of Land Policy, Cambridge, 2006).
  - "Race, Poverty and the Humane Metropolis: Revisiting William H. Whyte," The Human Metropolis: People and Nature in the 21st Century City (published book chapter), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 9)